 <resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bhopal Travel Guide</string>

    <!-- Van vihar-->
    <string name="van_vihar">Van Vihar</string>
    <string name="van_vihar_address">Shymala Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462002
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="van_vihar_opening_hours">The park is open to the visitors from 6:30AM to 7:00PM.
        \nIt is closed on Friday.
        \nThe best time to visit the park is from July to September</string>
    <string name="van_vihar_entry_fees">1. Individual on Foot / Cycling \n* ₹20 For Indians.\n* ₹30 For Foreigner.
                                        \n\n2. 2 Wheelers (Max 2 persons per Vehicle)	\n* ₹60.
                                        \n\n3. Auto Rickshaw (Max 4 persons including driver)	\n* ₹120.
                                        \n\n4. Car / Light Vehicles / SUVs (Max 8 persons including driver) \n* ₹250.
    </string>
    <string name="van_vihar_website"><a href = "http://www.mptourism.com/blog/places-to-visit-in-bhopal-van-vihar-national-park.html">http://www.mptourism.com/blog/places-to-visit-in-bhopal-van-vihar-national-park.html</a></string>
    <string name="van_vihar_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_van_vihar">Van Vihar National Park is no doubt an amazing mix of rich biota and swanky green settings.
                    Its time to take your wanderlust to all new levels with one of our unexplored hidden gems.

        \n\nA park made from a depleted forest!
        \n\nBestowed with some great local markets, ancient palaces, glittering lakes, divine temples, majestic mosques and a national park,
        the capital city of Madhya Pradesh has it all! However, this piece of knowledge will primarilyspeak
        about one of the best national parks in India and Madhya Pradesh i.e. Van Vihar National Park.
        \n\nVan Vihar National Park was formed from a depleted forest area. In order to bring back and protect the rich flora fauna,
        this unproductive land was declared a National Park in 1981 under the wildlife protection act.

        \n\nThe rich wildlife at Van Vihar!
        \n\nThis open zoological park comprises some huge wire enclosures where the carnivores like tiger, lion, panther, bear,
        and hyena stay as per the modern theory of the zoo management. On the contrary, the herbivores for instance cheetal
        and blackbuck are allowed to move around freely. The relentless chirping of a wide range of birds fills the air with
        vivacity while crocodile and tortoises relax in the sun. Another division which needs a mention here is the reptile unit,
        where one can see snakes like the cobras,
        russel vipers and pythons crawling on mud. The Van ViharRashtriyaUdyan also houses a ginormous variety of butterflies and insects.

       \n\n The best way to explore Van Vihar National Park

\n\nBesides the options of travelling the park via car or motorcycle, we would recommend you to explore the beauty of thisgreen
        setup on a bicycle or just walk around. After reaching the gate of Van Vihar National Park,
        you get the option of hiring a bike on rent else you can also carry your own if you wish to.
    </string>


    <!-- BIRLA MANDIR-->
    <string name="birla_mandir_txt">Birla Mandir</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir_address">Arera Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462011 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir_opening_hours">Timings : 7:00 AM to 12:00 PM, \n3:00 PM to 9:00 PM.\n All days of the week</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir_entry_fees">NO ENTRY FEE</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_birla_mandir">
        Built at the summit of Arera hills is the Lakshmi Narayan Temple, structured with grandiose scale and design.
        The temple is more commonly known as Birla Mandir. Its an awe-inspiring spectacle that showcases a panoramic
        view of the historic city of Bhopal. The temple was built in the honour of Lakshmi, the deity of wealth and
        her consort Vishnu (also known by the name Narayan), the preserver of the universe. Hence the name Lakshmi
        Narayan. Surrounded by greenery and an ancient charm, the temple is a shrine to Lord Shiva and Parvathi,
        providing solace and tranquillity to devotees.
        \n\nSpread over 7.5 acres adorned with well-maintained lawns and gardens, fountains and sculptures the grand
        temple attracts thousands of devotees during the festivities of Janmashtami and Diwali. The Lakshmi Narayan
        Temple was erected by the famous industrial family - the Birla Group and inaugurated by Mahatma Gandhi.
        \n\nThe Birla Temple also houses the famous Birla Museum in its premises with collections dating back to
        the 12th-century boasting some sculptures from the era of Paramaras. A magnificent archway welcomes devotees
        at the entrance that leads to a picturesque of finely crafted Hindu sculptures. The sandy-yellowish colour of
        the temple and the contagious greenery of the gardens adds an antique appeal to its ambience.
    </string>


    <!-- SANCHI STOOP-->
    <string name="sanchi">Sanchi Stupa</string>
    <string name="sanchi_address">Sanchi, Raisen, \nMadhya Pradesh,464661, \nIndia</string>
    <string name="sanchi_opening_hours">Sanchi Stupa timings are from 8:30 AM to
                                         5:30 PM on all days of the week.\nTimings for Sanchi Stupa Museum are 10 am to 5 pm.</string>
    <string name="sanchi_entry_fees">* ₹10 For Indians.\n* ₹250 For Foreigner</string>
    <string name="sanchi_website"><a href = "http://www.mptourism.com/tourist-places/sanchi-stupa.html">http://www.mptourism.com/tourist-places/sanchi-stupa.html</a></string>
    <string name="sanchi_visit_duration">2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_sanchi">Sanchi Stupa is a Buddhist complex, famous for its Great Stupa,
        on a hilltop at Sanchi Town in Raisen District of the State of Madhya Pradesh,
        India. It is located in 46 kilometres (29 mi) north-east of Bhopal, capital of Madhya Pradesh.
        The Great Stupa at Sanchi is one of the oldest stone structures in India, and an important monument of Indian Architecture.
        It was originally commissioned by the emperor Ashoka in the 3rd century BCE. Its nucleus was a simple hemispherical brick
        structure built over the relics of the Buddha. It was crowned by the chhatri, a parasol-like structure symbolising high rank,
        which was intended to honour and shelter the relics. The original construction work of this stupa was overseen by Ashoka,
        whose wife Devi was the daughter of a merchant of nearby Vidisha. Sanchi was also her birthplace as well as the venue of her and
        Ashokas wedding. In the 1st century BCE, four elaborately carved toranas (ornamental gateways) and a balustrade encircling the entire
        structure were added.
        The Sanchi Stupa built during Mauryan period was made of bricks. The composite flourished until the 11th century.
    </string>


    <!-- UPPER LAKE-->
    <string name="upper_lake">Upper Lake</string>
    <string name="upper_lake_address">Upper Lake, Near CM House, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh, 462003, \nIndia</string>
    <string name="upper_lake_opening_hours">6:00 am – 7:00 pm\nAll days of The Week</string>
    <string name="upper_lake_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
        \n\nBoating Prices
    \n* ₹100 per person for Cruise boat (Ride of 45 minutes)
    \n* ₹240 per person for Motor Boat
    \n* ₹80 per person for Paddle Boat</string>
    <string name="upper_lake_website"><a href = "https://bhopaltourism.in/upper-lake-bhopal">https://bhopaltourism.in/upper-lake-bhopal</a></string>
    <string name="upper_lake_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_upper_lake">The oldest man made lake in India, Upper lake is also known as Bhojtal or Bada Talab locally.
        This beautiful and vast water body was built during the 11th century. The lake is a massive earthen bound construction, built
        across the Kolans River. According to a legend, it is believed that King Bhoj constructed this gigantic lake to cure his skin disease.
        \n\nThe Upper lake is spread over a catchment area of 36.1 sq km, and it happens to be the major source of potable water for the
        people of Bhopal. Within the vicinity of the lake, there is an attractive royal garden called Kamla Park, which makes its
        surroundings more scenic. The hub of all water sport activities in Bhopal, the lake is a favourite spot for adventure enthusiasts.
        The Upper (and bigger) Lake is separated from the smaller one by an overbridge. A boat club, walkway and aquarium, serenaded by a
        cool breeze, makes the Upper Lake area delightful for a rendezvous. The lake also has the dargah of Shah Ali Shah, a maulvi.
    </string>

    <!-- YODHASTHAL ARMY MUSEUM-->
    <string name="yodhasthal_museum">Yodhasthal Army museum</string>
    <string name="yodhasthal_museum_address">Airport Rd, Lalghati, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462038 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="yodhasthal_museum_opening_hours">Tuesday - Sunday \n9:00 AM - 1:00 PM ; \n5:00 PM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="yodhasthal_museum_entry_fees">No Entry Fee</string>
    <string name="yodhasthal_museum_website"><a href = "https://www.facebook.com/Yodhasthal/?rf=1770097863261739">https://www.facebook.com/Yodhasthal/?rf=1770097863261739</a></string>
    <string name="yodhasthal_museum_visit_duration">2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_yodhasthal_museum">
        Yodhasthal, the army museum in Bhopal a prominent "Know your Army" facility, is known for its exhibition of arms
        and ammunition used by defence forces. The museum provides engrossing knowledge about the victories and war stories
        of Indian Army. Dedicated to the youth of Bhopal, Yodhasthal offers enriching audio-visual experience about the defence
        with displays of arty guns, tanks, arms used on the battlefield before and after independence. The war equipment
        narrates the splendid history of all the wars ever fought in the past.

        \nThe state museum and tribal museum of Madhya Pradesh are two other museums 6 km away from Yodhasthal. Inaugurated by
        the General Officer Commanding of Headquarters Bhopal, Major General Narinder Pal Singh, the museum is an aesthetic
        structure. Creating awareness among youngsters through exhibiting the finery of Indian Army, therefore encouraging
        more youngsters to commit to this profession was a significant motive of the museum.
    </string>

    <!-- TAJ-UL-MASJID-->
    <string name="taj_ul_masjid_name">Taj-Ul-Masjid</string>
    <string name="taj_ul_masjid_address">NH 12, Kohefiza, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462001 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="taj_ul_masjid_opening_hours"> \n6:00 am – 8:00 pm; \nAll Days Of The Week\n\nNote: Entry to the mosque however,
        is not allowed to non-Muslims on Fridays</string>
    <string name="taj_ul_masjid_entry_fees">No Entry Fee</string>
    <string name="taj_ul_masjid_website"><a href = "https://bhopal.nic.in/en/tourist-place/taj-ul-masajid/">https://bhopal.nic.in/en/tourist-place/taj-ul-masajid</a></string>
    <string name="taj_ul_masjid_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_taj_ul_masjid">
        Despite popular belief, the largest mosque in India is not the Jama Masjid of Delhi. It is, in fact, the Taj-ul-Masjid,
        in the central India town of Bhopal, which is the capital of the state of Madhya Pradesh. With an interior area of about
        430,000 square feet, the mosque has a capacity of 175,000 people.
        \nThe meaning of Taj-ul-Masjid translates to ‘The Crown of Mosques,’ and the magnificent architecture reflects just that.
        The masjid was built between the years 1868 and 1901, started by Sultan Shah Jehan Begum of Bhopal. Not only is the mosque
        the largest in the country, but it also happens to be the second largest mosque in Asia. Made of red stone, the mosque is
        situated by the lake referred to as the Motia Talab.
        \nThe mosque has three domes and two minarets. The masjid is open on all days, but non-Muslims are not allowed inside on
        Fridays. A sign of determination of the female ruler, the mosque is also a symbol of devotion. The mosque holds remarkable
        similarity with the architecture of Jama Masjid of Delhi, including the decorations.

        \nWhile the construction of the mosque began in the 1800s, it was stalled due to lack of funds. Construction started again in
        1971, and through the efforts of Maulana Sayed Hashmat Ali Sahab of Bhopal and Allama Mohammad Imran Khan Nadwi Azhari, the
        mosque was completely built by 1985. During this stage of construction, the entrance, which is also the eastern gate, was
        renovated in a very grand manner.

        \nBhopal is well connected with Delhi and Bombay, and once in the city, reaching Taj-ul-Masjid is not much of a hassle. The
        location is prime, and the place is one of the important landmarks of the city.
    </string>

    <!-- KANHA FUN CITY-->
    <string name="kanha_fun_city">Kanha Fun City</string>
    <string name="kanha_fun_city_address">Hoshangabad Rd, Indus Towne, \nRatanpur Sadak, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462047 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="kanha_fun_city_opening_hours">10:00 am – 6:00 pm; \nAll Days Of The Week</string>
    <string name="kanha_fun_city_entry_fees">The mentioned price is for an adult and includes entry to Amusement Park.
                                    \n\n* Water Park + Amusement Park: INR 450 per adult
                                    \n* Senior Citizens: Free</string>
    <string name="kanha_fun_city_website"><a href ="http://kanhafuncity.com/">kanhafuncity.com</a></string>
    <string name="kanha_fun_city_visit_duration">2 to 3 hrs</string>
     <string name="about_kanha_fun_city">
       Kanha Fun City is an amusement and water park located in the city of Bhopal. This park has a wide range of thrill
        and water rides making it an ideal destination for the entire family to visit. Rides in the amusement park include
        Swing Chair, Family Train, Water MGR, Bungee Jump, Jumping Frog, Dashing Car, Flying Dutchman, Rainbow, Mono Cycle,
        Vortex and many more. The water park has many slides and attractions like Wave Pool, Multiply System, Baby Pool, Aqua
        Disco, Turning Point, Tube Slide, Cyclone, Body Slide and Family Slide. Kanha Fun City also has five venues which can host
        events like wedding reception, theme parties, corporate parties, school functions, picnics, and product launches.
    </string>

    <!-- SAIR SAPATA-->
    <string name="sair_sapata">Sair Sapata</string>
    <string name="sair_sapata_address">Bhadbhada Road, Prempura, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462044 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="sair_sapata_opening_hours">11:00 AM - 10:00 PM; \nAll Days Of The Week</string>
    <string name="sair_sapata_entry_fees">* Adults: ₹30
                                        \n* Children: ₹10</string>
    <string name="sair_sapata_website"><a href = "https://www.facebook.com/SairSapataBhopal/">https://www.facebook.com/SairSapataBhopal</a></string>
    <string name="sair_sapata_visit_duration">2 to 3 hrs</string>
    <string name="about_sair_sapata">
       Sair Sapata is a significant entertainment zone, inaugurated on 29 September 2011. The tourism complex is predominantly
        a play park which is also a good leisure space for adults. Covering an area of 24.56 acres, Sair Sapata offers enjoyable
        activities like forest hiking, car dashing, zorbing and so on. Boat rides, four kiosks and three viewpoints keep tourists engaged.

        \n\nThe complex has attractions that actively encourage tourism, like two acres of childrens play area, musical fountain, toy
        train and a suspension bridge. Situated on the banks of the Bada Talaab (Upper Lake) of Bhopal, the suspension bridge is a
        significant attraction. Built with RCC deck slabs along the lines of Lachman Jhula, it is believed to be the first pedestrian
        bridge made this way in India. With a motive to extend tourist facilities, Madhya Pradesh State Tourism Development Corporation
        renovated and developed Sair Sapata.
    </string>

    <!-- PEOPLES MALL-->
    <string name="peoples_mall">People\'s Mall</string>
    <string name="peoples_mall_address">People\'s Campus, Bhanpur, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462037 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="peoples_mall_opening_hours">9:00AM to 9:00PM \nAll Days Of The Week.</string>
    <string name="peoples_mall_entry_fees">* Amusement park entry fee: Rs.50/- per person
                                           \n* Peoples mall water park bhopal ticket price: Rs.350/- per person
\n* Prices of individual attractions vary.</string>
    <string name="peoples_mall_website"><a href = "https://www.facebook.com/PeoplesWorldBhopal/">https://www.facebook.com/PeoplesWorldBhopal/</a></string>
    <string name="peoples_mall_visit_duration">3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_peoples_mall">
        An amusement park plus shopping mall in Bhopal. The People\'s mall is loved for its number of life-size replicas including
        the Taj Mahal, Red Fort, Eiffel tower, Lotus temple, the Statue of Liberty, Egyptian Pyramids and the India Gate. The place
        offers some of the best eateries in the city and a number of shops that are perfect to spoil yourself with some retail therapy!

        \n\nPeople\'s mall highlights include:


        \n* Children\'s Gaming center
        \n* Cinema Hall
        \n* Blowing fare
        \n* Water Park

    </string>

    <!-- DB CITY MALL-->
    <string name="db_city_mall">Db City Mall</string>
    <string name="db_city_mall_address">Zone - I Hoshangabad Road, \nBhopal 462063 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="db_city_mall_opening_hours">10:30AM to 11:00PM \nAll Days Of The Week.</string>
    <string name="db_city_mall_website"><a href = "http://www.dbcity.in/">http://www.dbcity.in/</a></string>
    <string name="db_city_mall_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_db_city_mall">
        Spread over 13 lacs sq.ft of floor space, “DB City” is one of the largest shopping centers in central India housing
        over 135 Indian and international brands and f&amp;b outlets under one roof. It is the first shopping mall in Bhopal and city
        has witnessed its opening in Aug, 2010. Mall is Located at the gist of the central business district, one of the galvanizing
        territory of the city. DB City has carefully cherry picked mix of brands providing optimum choice to the consumer in shopping,
        entertainment, food and leisure. Courtyard Marriott hotel recently opened.

        \n\nMall is witnessing over 10 lacs footfall per month which goes up to 18 lacs during festive season (Diwali, Christmas etc).
        DB Mall now has become city\'s landmark &amp; benchmark not just in shopping, but also in entertainment &amp; leisure activities.

    </string>

    <!--MANBHAWAN TEKRI-->
    <string name="manuabhan_tekri">Manuabhan Tekri</string>
    <string name="manuabhan_tekri_address">Sun City, Lalghati, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462038 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="manuabhan_tekri_opening_hours"> 06:30 AM - 08:00 PM \nAll Days Of The Week.
    \n\nRope Way Timings: 10:00 am to 7:00 pm &amp; will be closed from 1:00 pm to 3:30 pm
     Rope way open full day on Sunday and Public Holidays.</string>
    <string name="manuabhan_tekri_entry_fees">* No Entry Fee
                                              \n* ₹66 per person for two way RopeWay trip</string>
    <string name="manuabhan_tekri_website"><a href = "https://bhopaltourism.in/manua-bhan-ki-tekri-bhopal">https://bhopaltourism.in/manua-bhan-ki-tekri-bhopal</a></string>
    <string name="manuabhan_tekri_visit_duration">1 to 2 hours</string>
    <string name="about_manuabhan_tekri">
        Situated atop a hill is the beautiful Manua Bhan Ki Tekri, a famous pilgrimage spot for Jain devotees.
        Also known as Mahaveer Giri, it is known for its exquisite architecture and panoramic views of the city.
        The tekri houses the footwear of Jain saint Shri Jindutta Sureshwarji, Maharaj Shri Vijay Suriji and Acharya Manutung,
        along with an idol of Shri Man Bhadarji.
        \n\nThe Simha Gate of the temple features an old manuscript carved on stone, interestingly the language in which it
        is written is still to be deciphered. It is said to be the Sadhana Sthali of Oswal Dynasty. On the event of Kartik Purnima,
        a big fare is held in the temple every year.
        \n\nThe temple is situated on top of the hill near Lal Ghati. To reach here you can either take the ropeway up the hill
        or walk up from the base of the hill.


    </string>

    <!--INDIRA GANDHI RASHTRIYA MANAV SANGRAHALAY-->
    <string name="manav_sangrahalay">Indira Gandhi Rashtriya Manav Sangrahalay</string>
    <string name="manav_sangrahalay_address">Lake View Road, Next to RCE campus, \nShymala Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462013 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="manav_sangrahalay_opening_hours"> March to August 11.00 to 18.30 and September to Feb 10.00 to 17.30.
                                                \nOpens on  Every day except Mondays and National Holidays.</string>
    <string name="manav_sangrahalay_entry_fees">* Free Entry : Children up to 12 years.
                                                \n* Entry tickets, Rs. 50/- per head and Rs. 25/- concessional charges for students and groups.
                                                \n* Entry of the children age below 12 years is free. Visitors and for students on production of Identity cards.
    </string>
    <string name="manav_sangrahalay_website"><a href = "http://igrms.gov.in/">http://igrms.gov.in/</a></string>
    <string name="manav_sangrahalay_visit_duration">2 to 3 hours</string>
    <string name="about_manav_sangrahalay">
        The open-air exhibitions include Himalayan Village, Medicinal Trail, Mythological Trails, Desert Village and Rock-Art Heritage
        that displays 36 rock shelters with stunning prehistoric paintings. There is also an artistically designed indoor museum called
        Veethi Sankul. The enclosed museum exhibits a collection of traditional outfits, agricultural &amp; household objects and other crafts
        showcasing the regime of the tribes!
        \n\nThe museum gives visitors a great opportunity to do trekking and cycling. Along with that, they can also discover more
        than 50 dwells of Indian tribal communities living in different climates and locations of the country. The fine infrastructure
        with winding roads amidst the sprawling green forest, bring joy to the travellers who want to unwind and gain a holistic experience.

        \n\nThe premises of Indira Gandhi Rashtriya Manav Sangrahalaya are alive all year round through numerous events. From
        educational programmes, open-air plays, exhibitions, workshops, literature fest, dance recitals to other tribal festivals,
        the museum is deeply dedicated to its core mandates i.e. to support, promote and celebrate the cultural diversity of India
        in every possible way. Simply put, IGRMS symbolises new museum movement in India where tribal and folk communities nurture
        their dream in order to head the sustainable future.
        \nIt is an ideal destination to indulge in soft-adventure activities while admiring the beauty of nature!
    </string>

    <!--GOHAR MAHAL-->
    <string name="gohar_mahal">Gohar Mahal</string>
    <string name="gohar_mahal_address">VIP Road, Nakkar Khana, \nPeer Gate Area, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462001 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="gohar_mahal_opening_hours">All days of the week.\n8:00 AM - 6:00 PM</string>
    <string name="gohar_mahal_entry_fees">* No entry fee.</string>
    <string name="gohar_mahal_website"><a href = "https://bhopaltourism.in/gohar-mahal-bhopal">https://bhopaltourism.in/gohar-mahal-bhopal</a></string>
    <string name="gohar_mahal_visit_duration">1 hour</string>
    <string name="about_gohar_mahal">
        Constructed in the year 1820 by the first woman ruler of Bhopal, Gohar Begum this is one of the most beautiful structures in Bhopal.
        The palace was built with a perfect blend of Hindu and Mughal styles of architecture. Gohar Mahal has lost some of its original
        charm over the years, but it is undergoing restoration which will bring back its grandeur.
    </string>

    <!--BIRLA MUSEUM-->
    <string name="birla_museum">Birla Museum</string>
    <string name="birla_museum_address">Arera Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462011 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="birla_museum_opening_hours">All days of the week.\n10:00 AM - 5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="birla_museum_entry_fees">* ₹30 per person.</string>
    <string name="birla_museum_website"><a href = "https://bhopaltourism.in/gohar-mahal-bhopal">https://bhopaltourism.in/gohar-mahal-bhopal</a></string>
    <string name="birla_museum_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_birla_museum">
        The Birlas are one of the biggest names associated with the industrial development in India. They are the pioneers
        in the field of Science and Technology in the country; and the Birla Children\'s Museum serves this purpose to the fullest.
        The Birla Group has taken this initiative in Kolkata and had established a museum to display their achievements and offer
        opportunity for the younger generation to learn the basic concepts of science. The museum was established in 1956 and it
        has ever since been the favourite place for the science lovers and students who are interested in this field.
        \n\nVisit this museum to witness a wide spectrum of galleries and design works that ranges from basic to advanced science
        including nuclear, mining, communication, electronics, iron and steel etc. There are a lot of activities that are being
        organised in the museum including game shows, sky watch sessions, movie screening, fun-filled learning sessions and a lot
        more. Another section in  Birla Children\'s Museum includes an aquarium, aviary, rabbit house, bonsai plants, snake pits and
        underground coal mine to offer a deep insight into the field.

    </string>
    
    <!--ARCHAEOLOGICAL MUSEUM -->
    <string name="archaeological_museum">Archaeological Museum</string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum_address">Shyamla Hills Rd, NITTTR Campus, \nShymala Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh, 462002 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum_opening_hours">All days of the week Except Monday.\n10:30 AM - 5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum_entry_fees">* ₹10 for Indians
                                \n* ₹100 for Foreigners
                                \n* ₹50 for Still Camera
                                \n ₹200 for Video Camera</string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum_website"><a href = "https://bhopaltourism.in/state-archaeological-museum-bhopal">https://bhopaltourism.in/state-archaeological-museum-bhopal</a></string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_archaeological_museum">
        Bhopal which is appropriately called as the “City of Lakes”, is a wonderful city located in central India. It is the
        capital city of Madhya Pradesh located on the Malwa plateau. Culturally Bhopal is a wealthy city and is burgeoning as
        a major tourist destination in Central India. The city boasts its unrivalled charm and is the home to a lot of museums
        and galleries of which State Archaeological Museum, Bhopal is worthy of a visit. It has a lot of informative and remarkable
        artifacts belonging to the historic era of Madhya Pradesh.
        \n\nArchaeological Museum of Bhopal holds a significant place among the monuments and museums of Bhopal. The museum is
        the miniature form of the rich traditions of the state. The important things to watch are paintings of different schools,
        statues the Hindu Goddess of Wealth also called as Lakshmi, and magnificent statues of Buddha.

    </string>

    <!--Shaukat Mahal -->
    <string name="shaukat_mahal">Shaukat Mahal</string>
    <string name="shaukat_mahal_address">Sultania Rd, Nakkar Khana, \nPeer Gate Area, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462001 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="shaukat_mahal_opening_hours">All days of the week Except Friday.\n7:00 am – 7:00 pm (1st Apr to 30th Sep)
\n7:00 am – 6:00 pm (1st Oct to 31st Mar)</string>
    <string name="shaukat_mahal_entry_fees">No Entry Fee</string>
    <string name="shaukat_mahal_website"><a href = "https://bhopaltourism.in/shaukat-mahal-bhopal">https://bhopaltourism.in/shaukat-mahal-bhopal</a></string>
    <string name="shaukat_mahal_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_shaukat_mahal">
       One of the architectural wonders of Bhopal, Shaukat Mahal features an exquisite amalgamation of Indo-Islamic and European
        styles of architecture. Given its architecture, it is believed that this palace was designed by a Frenchman and is thus very
        different from the rest of the Islamic architecture in the locality. Post-Renaissance and Gothic styles have been combined in
        the construction of the palace, which are reflected in its architectural beauty.
        \n\nThe palace is made of white alabaster, and features a series of complicated triangular-shaped arches on the ceiling.
        The exterior walls are adorned with delicate floral patterns.There is a brick-red building of Sadar Manzil, adjoining the
        palace which once served as the hall of public audience and is surrounded by beautiful gardens.

    </string>
    
    
    <!--Bharat bhawan -->
    <string name="bharat_bhawan">Bharat Bhawan</string>
    <string name="bharat_bhawan_address">Bharat Bhawan Rd, Near Upper Lake, \nKrishna Nagar, Shymala Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462013 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bharat_bhawan_opening_hours">
        All days of the week except Monday
        \n2:00 PM - 8:00 PM (Feb - Oct)
        \n1:00 PM - 7:00 PM (Nov - Jan)
    </string>
    <string name="bharat_bhawan_entry_fees">₹10 per person entry fee</string>
    <string name="bharat_bhawan_website"><a href = "http://bharatbhawan.org/">http://bharatbhawan.org/</a></string>
    <string name="bharat_bhawan_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_bharat_bhawan">

        Inaugurated by the then Prime Minister of India, Shrimati Indira Gandhi on 13th February 1982, Bharat Bhavan is multi art centre
        set up to create an interactive proximity between the verbal, visual and performing arts. It provides space for contemporary
        expression, thought, quest and innovation. Bharat Bhavan seek to provide a creative and thought provoking milieu to those
        who wish to contribute something new and meaningful, in contemporary scene in the fine arts, literature, theatre, cinema,
        dance and music. It houses some of the best and most lasting that is being created in our towns, villages and forests.

        \n\nCharles Correa the architect found here the possibilities of a series of terraced gardens, which would be seen cascading
        down to the lake. The visitors enter at the highest level and walk down a pedestrian spine, flanked by a pattern of courtyards,
        to reach the various parts of the complex. Each curve and space defines itself. Each of the part of the building is distinct
        yet flows easily one another, linked by meandering paths. The total effect is one of the surprise and pleasure. There is always
        a moment when the eye can rest and the mind contemplates.

        The activities of Bhart Bhavan are organized through its wings.

    </string>

    <!--RAISEN FORT -->
    <string name="raisen_fort">Raisen Fort</string>
    <string name="raisen_fort_address">Raisen, Madhya Pradesh 464551 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="raisen_fort_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n10:00 AM - 5:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="raisen_fort_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_raisen_fort">

        Raisen Fort is a substantial historical edifice placed atop a hill enthralling a vast water reservoir, palaces and a few
        temples within the fort. Located in the city of Bhopal, the 800-year-old fort has nine gateways, fortifications, domes and
        the remains of several buildings from the early medieval period. It\'s now an abode to hundreds of bats.
        \n\nRaisen fort is also a shrine of a Muslim saint Hazrat Peer Fatehullah Shah Baba. It is believed that the shrine can
        fulfil the desires of the pilgrims. Until the 16th century, the fort was under the hegemony of the Rajputs and other Hindu
        rulers. Although the nawabs of Bhopal initially captured the fort, it is presently under the custody of ASI. The magnificent
        fort stands on an outlier of a rock which has a massive stone wall pierced with nine gateways. It drowns in a wilderness and
        a thick undergrowth of vegetation and wild long grass. Adorned with a large courtyard and a beautiful pool in the middle, the
        origin of the Raisen fort dates back to the 1200 AD. With four palaces (Badal Mahal, Rohini Mahal, Itradaan Mahal &amp; Hawa Mahal)
        within its boundaries, the mighty fort also houses a temple dedicated to Lord Shiva. The doors of the temple open every year on
        the occasion of Shivratri. The pilgrims who visit the temple on other days tie a piece of cloth on the grill gate for the fulfilment
        of their wishes. Raisen fort also abounds rock shelters with paintings created by the cave dwellers.

    </string>

    <!--Bhojpur temple -->
    <string name="bhojpur_temple">Bhojpur Temple</string>
    <string name="bhojpur_temple_address">Bhojpur Madhya Pradesh 464551,
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bhojpur_temple_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 am – 7:00 pm
    </string>
    <string name="bhojpur_temple_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_bhojpur_temple">
        The enigmatic temple of Bhojpur is an incomplete Hindu temple situated in the Bhojpur Village of Madhya Pradesh.
        Dedicated to Lord Shiva, it houses a 7.5 feet high lingam in its sanctum and is believed to have been constructed
        in the 11th century during the reign of King Bhoja. The temple\'s construction was left abandoned for reasons that
        are still unknown. Construction material can still be found at the site, with architectural plans engraved on the
        surrounding rocks. Historians speculate that it could be due to a sudden natural disaster, war or lack of resources.
        The temple has been designated as a Monument of National Importance by the Archaeological Survey of India (ASI).
        \n\nThere are many theories revolving around what may have happened that led to the abandonment of the Bhojpuri
        Temple\'s construction. One theory is presented by the peculiar construction style of the edifice, where the temple
        does not have a \'Mandapa\' connected to the inner sanctum. Another unique construction feature is the temple\'s
        rectilinear roof which defies the typical curvilinear dome tower. These divergences have led some to believe that
        Bhojpur Temple was perhaps a funerary monument constructed by Bhoja for the peace of soul of his father Sindhuraja
        or of his uncle Munja. The lingam in the Bhojpur Temple is built using three superimposed limestone blocks with a
        height of 7.5 feet and a circumference of 17.8 feet. The total height of the lingam is 40 feet with a square platform
        as a base. It is the tallest lingam of its kind in the world.

    </string>


    <!--Malai temple -->
    <string name="malai_temple">Shri Madhya Swami Malai Temple</string>
    <string name="malai_temple_address">Slum Area, Arera Colony, Bhopal,\nMadhya Pradesh 462039
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="malai_temple_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n8:30 AM to 12:00 PM
        \n2:00 AM to 6:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="malai_temple_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_malai_temple">
        Sri Kanchi Kamakoti mutt, a Goshala set up at Madhya Swamimalai Mandir, Bhopal.A temple
        of Sri Kanchi math was estblished in 1984.The Shankaracharya of the kanchi math is the main priest for all the kanchi
        math temple.lord Karthikeya is mainly worshipped although shrine of other gods can also be found here. This is one of
        the famous Hindu temple in India.
        \n\nThis temple is located in Arera Colony, Bhopal. 15 kms from Bhopal main railway station.
        \n35 years oldest hill rock temple and maintained by Kanchi Kamakotti Pettam, Kanchipuram.
        \n\nLord Swaminatha or Karthikeya is the presiding deity of the Madhya Swamimalai Temple.In addition to the presiding
        deity, other shrines located in the temple include Ishwarya Ganapathi temple(Ganesh ji Mandir),Lord Ekambaranatha
        temple(Shivji Mandir),Devi Kamakshi temple(Devi Mandir),Navagrahs Mandir(Nine Divine planets),Lord Hanuman temple
        (Maruti Mandir),Lord Venkateshwara temple(Balaji Mandir),Lord Naga devatha temple,Lord Sri Krishna temple,Paduka Mandir.

    </string>
    
    
    <!--Mata Mandir-->
    <string name="mata_mandir">Mata Mandir</string>
    <string name="mata_mandir_address">Near Budhni, \nSehore District, Salkanpur, \nMadhya Pradesh 466446,
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="mata_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -10:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="mata_mandir_visit_duration">2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_mata_mandir">
        Devoted to one of the incarnations of goddess Durga, the presiding deity in Salkanpur Temple is of Ma Durga Beejasan.
        It is also linked to the legend of the Shaktipeeth in Hindu mythology, where temples were created on spots where parts
        of Goddess Parvati\'s charred body fell.
        \n\nEven though the temple is quite old, but it is well maintained and renovated by Salkanpur Trust. The temple is perched
        on a 244 meters high hillock and has more than 1000 stairs. Those of you who don\'t want to take the stairs can use the
        ropeway service, an easier way to reach the temple. Through the ropeway, you will reach the back entrance of the temple.
        The ropeway goes over a pond, through the forest area to the hill top, offering panoramic views of the surroundings.

    </string> 
    
    <!--jain Mandir-->
    <string name="jain_mandir">jain Mandir</string>
    <string name="jain_mandir_address">sun city,Lalghati, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462030
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="jain_mandir_opening_hours">
       06:30 AM - 08:00 PM \nAll Days Of The Week.
    \n\nRope Way Timings: 10:00 am to 7:00 pm &amp; will be closed from 1:00 pm to 3:30 pm
     Rope way open full day on Sunday and Public Holidays.

    </string>
    <string name="jain_mandir_entry_fees">* No Entry Fee
                                              \n* ₹66 per person for two way RopeWay trip</string>
    <string name="jain_mandir_visit_duration">2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_jain_mandir">
        Situated atop a hill is the beautiful Manua Bhan Ki Tekri, a famous pilgrimage spot for Jain devotees.
        Also known as Mahaveer Giri, it is known for its exquisite architecture and panoramic views of the city.
        The tekri houses the footwear of Jain saint Shri Jindutta Sureshwarji, Maharaj Shri Vijay Suriji and Acharya Manutung,
        along with an idol of Shri Man Bhadarji.
        \n\nThe Simha Gate of the temple features an old manuscript carved on stone, interestingly the language in which it
        is written is still to be deciphered. It is said to be the Sadhana Sthali of Oswal Dynasty. On the event of Kartik Purnima,
        a big fare is held in the temple every year.
        \n\nThe temple is situated on top of the hill near Lal Ghati. To reach here you can either take the ropeway up the hill
        or walk up from the base of the hill.

    </string> 
    
    
    <!--kali Mandir-->
    <string name="kali_mandir">kali Mandir</string>
    <string name="kali_mandir_address">Near Thana Tallaiya, Sultania Road, Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="kali_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -10:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="kali_mandir_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_kali_mandir">
        The Shri Kalika Mandir temple has developed a place where the wishes of everyone are fulfilled. All religious people
        across the Country are visiting temples and making their life better-off by the blessings of Goddess Maa Kalika.
        \n\nThis Shri Kalika Mandir temple of Dakshin Kali at lower lake was Established by Shri Shiv Narayan Singh Bagwar
        with the consecrations of Goddess Maa Shri Kalika on Shrawan Shukl Ekadashi Vikram Samvat 2024 i.e. 3rd September,
        1968 and the temple has developed a place where the wishes of everyone is satisfied. Shri Kalika Mandir temple,
        Kalighat has been a center point amongst believers of Sakti and has developed as a Shakti Peeth over a period of
        time. A religious place of great significance for devotees across all segments by prolonged dedicated services of
        Shri Shiv Narayan Singh Bagwar.

    </string>



    <!--Gurudwara-->
    <string name="gurudwara">Gurudwara</string>
    <string name="gurudwara_address">Bhadbhada Road, Jawahar Chowk, \nStt Nagar, TT Nagar, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462003
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="gurudwara_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM -6:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="gurudwara_visit_duration">2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_gurudwara">
        A gurdwara is a place of assembly and worship for Sikhs. People from all faiths, and those who do not profess any faith
        , are welcomed in Sikh gurdwaras. Each gurdwara has a Darbar Sahib where the current and everlasting guru of the Sikhs,
        the scripture Guru Granth Sahib, is placed on a takhat (an elevated throne) in a prominent central position. The raagis
        (who sing Ragas) recite, sing and explain, the verses from the Guru Granth Sahib, in the presence of the congregation.

    </string>


    <!--DAUDI BOHRA MASJID-->
    <string name="daudi_bohra_masjid">Daudi Bohra Masjid</string>
    <string name="daudi_bohra_masjid_address">Saeed colony Berasia Road, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462038
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="daudi_bohra_masjid_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM -6:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="daudi_bohra_masjid_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_daudi_bohra_masjid">
        Dawoodi Bohra communities are united by a set of centuries-old principles: an unwavering commitment to the faith;
        being law-abiding citizens and developing a genuine love for the country in which they live; a belief in the value
        of society, education, hard work and empowering women; engagement with other faiths; and a responsibility to care
        for the environment and all creatures that dwell within it. They seek to embrace modernity while remaining true to
        their traditions and core beliefs.
        \n\nIn 2018, the Dawoodi Bohra community launched Project Rise, a global initiative established to improve the lives
        of people that are marginalized, neglected or living in poverty. Its upliftment programs span a range of policy areas,
        including healthcare, nutrition, hygiene, environmental responsibility and conservation, and education. Project Rise
        takes its inspiration from the teachings of Islam and the Prophetic traditions, which instruct Muslims to work for
        the betterment of others.

    </string>


    <!--DHAI SEEDHI MASJID-->
    <string name="dhai_seedhiki_masjid">Dhai Seedhi ki masjid</string>
    <string name="dhai_seedhiki_masjid_address">Medical College Campus, Kohefiza, Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="dhai_seedhiki_masjid_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM -6:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="dhai_seedhiki_masjid_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_dhai_seedhiki_masjid">
        Bhopal is not only home to Asia’s largest mosque, but to the oldest and tiniest mosque in the entire world as well!
        Situated inside the grounds of Hamidia Hospital, opposite to Taj-ul-Masjid, Dhai Seedhi ki Masjid is just four big
        steps by four big steps in area, making it about 16 sq m. acreage. Built on top of an old fort, this mosque has a
        watchtower of its own. According to locals, this is one of the oldest Bhopal mosques. This mosque came up as a
        makeshift mosque while the fort was being built and has continued to remain a place of worship ever since.
        \n The mosque was built as a praying place for the guards at the nearby fort.It is a photographer’s delight
        and one can come up with some excellent pictures here.

    </string>


    <!--VITTHAL MARKET MASJID-->
    <string name="vitthal_masjid">Vitthal Market masjid</string>
    <string name="vitthal_masjid_address">Ekant Park, Char Imli, Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462016
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="vitthal_masjid_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM -6:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="vitthal_masjid_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>


    <!--Sheetla Mata Mandir-->
    <string name="sheetla_mata_mandir">Sheetla Mata Mandir</string>
    <string name="sheetla_mata_mandir_address">Mataghat, Bada Talab, \nBhopal - 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="sheetla_mata_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -7:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="sheetla_mata_mandir_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>


    <!--Neori Mandir-->
    <string name="neori_mandir">Neori Mandir</string>
    <string name="neori_mandir_address">1, Neori Mandir Rd, BDA Colony, \nNayapura, Idgah Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="neori_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM -8:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="neori_mandir_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_neori_mandir">
        It is a structure designed to bring human beings and gods together, using symbolism to express the ideas and beliefs
        of Hinduism. The symbolism and structure of a Hindu temple are rooted in Vedic traditions, deploying circles
        and squares. It also represents recursion and equivalence of the macrocosm and the microcosm by astronomical
        numbers, and by "specific alignments related to the geography of the place and the presumed linkages of the deity
        and the patron". A temple incorporates all elements of Hindu cosmos—presenting the good, the evil and the
        human, as well as the elements of Hindu sense of cyclic time and the essence of life—symbolically presenting dharma,
        kama, artha, moksa, and karma.

    </string>


    <!--Gufa Mandir-->
    <string name="gufa_mandir">Gufa Mandir</string>
    <string name="gufa_mandir_address">Gufa mandir, Nayapura, Lalghati, \nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462030
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="gufa_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:30 AM - 7:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="gufa_mandir_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_gufa_mandir">
        Gufa Mandir positioned in the vicinity of Lalghati, is said to have been founded by Late Baba Narayan Das
        in 1949. Inside the building of the temple, statues of Lord Shiva, Ram - Laxman, Sitaji, Goddess Durga and
        Hanuman have been set up. The temple lures plenty of tourists from different parts of the world for darshan
        every day. Enclosing a Sanskrit college as well, this temple campus is easily accessible from anywhere in the city.

    </string>


    <!--Sai Mandir-->
    <string name="sai_mandir">Sai Baba Mandir</string>
    <string name="sai_mandir_address">E-6, Arera Colony, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462016
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="sai_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -8:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="sai_mandir_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_sai_mandir">
       Sai Baba is now revered as an incarnation of Sri Dattatreya and considered as Saguna Brahma by his devotees.
        He is attributed to be the creator, sustainer and destroyer of this universe by his devotees. He is decorated
        with jewels and all forms of Hindu vedic deities as he is believed by his followers to be the supreme God.
        \n\nAccording to Sri Pada Sri Vallabha charithra, Sripada Srivallabha the first incarnation of lord Dattatreya,
        had blessed lord Hanuman to be born as Sai Baba to spread the equality and spirituality with a message all are
        equal Sabka Malik Ek (Everyone\'s Master is One)

    </string>

    <!--Moti masjid-->
    <string name="moti_masjid">Moti Masjid</string>
    <string name="moti_masjid_address">Hawamahal Rd, Opposite Moti Masjid, \nChowki Talaiya, Talaiya, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="moti_masjid_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -7:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="moti_masjid_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_moti_masjid">
       Moti Masjid, also known as the Pearl Mosque, is situated in the heart of the city. A beautiful shrine, Moti
        Masjid signifies the history of the Bhopal Begums in India. Constructed in 1860 by Sikander Jehan Begum of
        Bhopal, the daughter of Qudisiya Begum, its architecture is more or less similar to the Jama Masjid in Delhi.
        Sikandar Begum, an unconventional and liberal women, abolished slavery. She used to dress up like a man usually
        and go out riding without a veil. She set the trend of progressive women in the city and thus Bhopal came to be
        known as the place of relatively liberated and progressive women.
        \n\nThe mosque stands majestically as a symbol of Bhopal\'s history and features a white marble facade with two
        small cupolas on the top. There are two dark red towers on either sides of the main building, adorned with bright
        golden spikes. These beautiful minarets are considered to be the gateway to heaven on earth and are used for the
        call to prayer for all faithful followers of Islam.


    </string>


    <!--Kalibari Mandir-->
    <string name="kalibari_mandir">Kalibari Mandir</string>
    <string name="kalibari_mandir_address">Awadhpuri, Piplani, BHEL, \nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462022
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="kalibari_mandir_opening_hours">
        All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -8:00 PM

    </string>
    <string name="kalibari_mandir_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_kalibari_mandir">
       The Kalibari at BHEL,Out of around 10,000 workers of the BHEL plant in Bhopal, there were 800 craftsmans and 200
        supervisory staff who were Bengalis.
        \n\nAs is unavoidable with the nearness of Bengalis, a Bangiya Sanskritik Parishad (BSP) was shaped in April 1960,
        with a library and perusing room offices at BHEL Bhopal. The Kali Puja, Durga Puja and Saraswati Puja begun to
        be sorted out yearly. Around 1963, the administration affirmed allotment of land under the non-exchanging social
        orders represent religious purposes. A real estate parcel was designated in composing under the plan, close Piplani,
        to the Bangiya Sanskritik Parishad by the BHEL Management. In 1967 a Kalibari samiti (affiliation) was shaped.

    </string>


    <!--Chintaman ganesh-->
    <string name="chintaman_ganesh">Shree Chintaman ganesh Temple</string>
    <string name="chintaman_ganesh_address">Sehore, Madhya Pradesh 466001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="chintaman_ganesh_opening_hours">
         All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -8:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="chintaman_ganesh_visit_duration">1 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_chintaman_ganesh">
      Chintaman Ganesh is an ancient holy and the biggest temple and of Lord Ganesha in Ujjain. As it is the temple
        of Ganesha, people take the blessings of Ganesh for starting every new venture. This temple is built across
        the Shipra river on the Fatehabad railway line. The temple is dedicated to Lord Ganesha, who is regarded as
        the Lord of beginnings as per the Hindu beliefs.
        \n\nIn the traditional times, the Lord is known as Chintaharan which literally means remover of all worries
        and tensions. The temple is thronged by crowds of people that come to do away with all their worries at the
        shrine of the Lord. The term Chintamani is another name used for Lord Vishnu, who is considered as the
        preserver of the Universe as per Hindu Mythology.

    </string>


    <!-- Bhimbetka -->
    <string name="bhim_betka">Rockshekter Of Bhimbetka</string>
    <string name="bhim_betka_address">Bhojpur Raisen, \nMadhya Pradesh 464990
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bhim_betka_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n6:30 AM -5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="bhim_betka_entry_fees">* ₹10 per person for Indians
  \n* ₹100 per person for foreign tourists
  \n* ₹50 per LMV for Indians
  \n* ₹20 per LMV for foreign tourists
  \n* ₹100 per mini bus for Indians
  \n* ₹400 per mini bus for foreign tourists
    </string>
    <string name="bhim_betka_website"><a href = "http://www.mptourism.com/tourist-places/bhimbetka-caves-rock-shelters.html">http://www.mptourism.com/tourist-places/bhimbetka-caves-rock-shelters.html</a></string>
    <string name="bhim_betka_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_bhim_betka">

Cave paintings dating back to approximately 30,000 years. Rock shelters that were home to humans, millennia ago. And a rich
        flora and fauna surrounding these, indeed, make Bhimbetka a gift to us from our earliest ancestors.
        \n\nAn archaeological treasure, Bhimbetka has around 243 rock shelters. The paintings found in the rock shelters here have a
        striking resemblance to the ones discovered in Kakadu National Park in Australia; to the cave paintings of Bushmen
        in Kalahari Desert and Upper Palaeolithic Lascaux cave paintings in France.
        \n\nA walkthrough these ancient naturally carved rocks surrounded by dense forests of Bhimbetka will bring alive
        child-like wonder in you.
    </string>


    <!-- Bhoj Wetland -->
    <string name="bhoj_wetland">Bhoj Wetland</string>
    <string name="bhoj_wetland_address">Near Upper &amp; Lower Lake, Bhopal,

 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bhoj_wetland_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n6:30 AM -5:30 PM</string>
    <string name="bhoj_wetland_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
        \n\nBoating Prices
    \n* ₹100 per person for Cruise boat (Ride of 45 minutes)
    \n* ₹240 per person for Motor Boat
    \n* ₹80 per person for Paddle Boat
    </string>
    <string name="bhoj_wetland_website"><a href = "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bhoj_Wetland">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bhoj_Wetland</a></string>
    <string name="bhoj_wetland_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_bhoj_wetland">
The Bhoj Wetland consists of two lakes located in the city of Bhopal, the capital of the central Indian state of Madhya Pradesh.
        The two lakes are the Bhojtal (Upper Lake) &amp; the Lower Lake, which lie to the west of the city center. The Bhojtal has
        an area of 31 km square, and drains a catchment or watershed of 361 km square. The watershed of the Bhojtal is mostly rural, with
        some urbanized areas around its eastern end. The lower lake has an area of 1.29 km square. Its catchment is 9.6 km square and
        is mostly urbanized; the Lower Lake also receives subsurface seepage from the Bhojtal.
        \n\nThe Bhojtal was created by Paramara Raja Bhoj (1005-1055), ruler of Malwa. He established Bhopal (also named after him)
        to secure the eastern frontier of his kingdom. The lake was created by constructing an earthen dam across the Kolans River.
        The Kolans was formerly a tributary of the Halali River; with the creation of the Bhojtal and a diversion channel, the upper
        reach of the Kolans River and the Bhojtal now drain into the Kaliasot River. Bhadbhada dam was constructed in 1965 at the
        southeast corner of the Bhojtal; it now controls the outflow to the Kaliasot river.
        \n\nThe Lower Lake was created in 1794 by Nawab Chhote Khan, Minister of Nawab Hayath Mohammad Khan, to beautify the
        city. It is also contained behind an earthen dam, and drains into the Halali River via the lower reach of the Kolans
        River, presently known as the Patra Drain. Both the Kaliasot and Halali Rivers are tributaries of the Betwa River.
        \n\nThe lakes are home to a diverse flora and fauna, including many waterbirds. They have been designated a wetland
        of international importance under the international Ramsar Convention since August 2002.    </string>


    <!-- Singhori Wild Life Sanctuary -->
    <string name="singhori_wild_life_sanctuary">Singhori Wild Life Sanctuary</string>
    <string name="singhori_wild_life_sanctuary_address">Kartoli, Madhya Pradesh 464986
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="singhori_wild_life_sanctuary_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n6:00 AM -9:00 PM</string>
    <string name="singhori_wild_life_sanctuary_website"><a href = "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/singhori_wild_life_sanctuary">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/singhori_wild_life_sanctuary</a></string>
    <string name="singhori_wild_life_sanctuary_visit_duration">2 to 3 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_singhori_wild_life_sanctuary">
    The Singhori Wildlife Sanctuary was established in the year 1976 spread over a total area of 288 sq. km. The Tiger,
    Leopard, Sambhar, Chital, Wild Boar, etc. are amongst the most spotted animal species here. Choukigarh Fort, Bhandariya
    Temple, and Caves of Jamgarh. On the Occasion of Shivratri, a fair is organized at various temples around the Sanctuary
    like the Bhandariya, Shiv Temple. Also places like Bhopal, Delabadi, Bhojpur, Pachmarhi are around the Sanctuary,
    which serve as wonderful touring spots for visitors. Forest Rest House, Bhandiv Forest Rest House Bumhori, P. W. D.
        Rest House, Bari is available for accommodation at the Sanctuary.</string>


    <!-- Kerwa dam -->
    <string name="kerwa_dam">Kerwa Dam</string>
    <string name="kerwa_dam_address">Kerwa Dam, Mendora, \nMadhya Pradesh 462007
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="kerwa_dam_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM to 6:00 PM.</string>
    <string name="kerwa_dam_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
         \n540 per person for Riding Ropeway
    </string>
    <string name="kerwa_dam_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_kerwa_dam">
        On a sunny day, the Kerwa Dam is the perfect spot to unwind and relax as you go boating, bird-watch or simply
        have a small picnic in the lush greenery all around.
        \n\nThe nearby Jungle camp is a favorite family spot where you can feel closer to nature and enjoy the view of
        the dam. The place offers adventure sports like Roping, Paintball, Rappelling and River Crossing. Don’t forget
        to carry your camera to capture the scenic beauty all around.    </string>

    <!-- Halali dam -->
    <string name="halali_dam">Halali Dam</string>
    <string name="halali_dam_address">Halali Dam, Madhya Pradesh,
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="halali_dam_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM to 6:00 PM.</string>
    <string name="halali_dam_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="halali_dam_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_halali_dam">
        Located 42 kilometers from Bhopal, the Halali Dam is a popular weekend spot. Whether you want to have a picnic here
        or simply want to go boating at the reservoir, the place promises to be a relaxing experience.
        \n\nOn sunny days, do prefer visiting the place in the early evening and enjoy the sunset as you sail in the water.
        The gorgeous view all around adds to the charm of the place.
        \n\nThe Halali reservoir is a reservoir in the Raisen district of Madhya Pradesh, India. It is built on the Halali River, 
        and lies 40 km away from the state capital Bhopal.The Halali River is a tributary of the Betwa River. It was formerly known as Thal River. In the 18th century, Dost Mohammad Khan\'s 
        forces killed a rival Rajput force near Jagdishpur (later renamed to Islamnagar) on the bank of the river. The river was 
        renamed to Halali river (the river of slaughter), because it appeared red with the blood of the victims.[3] Another name 
        for the river is Banganga.The Halali reservoir was commissioned in 1973
    </string>

    <!-- Bhadbhada dam -->
    <string name="bhadbhada_dam">Bhadbhada Dam</string>
    <string name="bhadbhada_dam_address">Suraj Nagar, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462044
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bhadbhada_dam_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n8:00 AM to 5:30 PM.</string>
    <string name="bhadbhada_dam_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="bhadbhada_dam_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_bhadbhada_dam">
       Built in 1960\’s, the Bhadbhada Dam is located on the Upper lake in Bhopal. The dam is used to regulate water flow
        in the Kaliasote river and consist of 11 gates. During the monsoon, the place is perfect for a day trip since the
        gates are opened.
        \nOn other days, the view of the lake and the river make for a great way to take a pit-stop as you explore the city.
    </string>

    <!-- Vardhman Park -->
    <string name="vardhman_park">Vardhman Park</string>
    <string name="vardhman_park_address">Lake View Walk Path, Kamla Park, \nKrishna Nagar, Shymala Hills, \nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="vardhman_park_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n9:00 AM to 10:30 PM.</string>
    <string name="vardhman_park_entry_fees">* ₹2 per person
  \n* ₹40 - 160 per person for ride
  \n* ₹200 per person for Package of 15 rides

    </string>
    <string name="vardhman_park_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_vardhman_park">
      A must visit for unlimited dose of fun and entertainment!  Vardhman Fantasy Park Mumbai  offers a lot of rides and
        it is the most popular amusement park of the city. It has a lot of open space and various kinds of events take place
        during the weekends. The food court here offers tasty yet affordable food. It is the most popular hang-out zone of the city.

    </string>


    <!-- kaliyasot dam -->
    <string name="kaliyasot_dam">Kaliyasot Dam</string>
    <string name="kaliyasot_dam_address">Kaliyasot Dam, \nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="kaliyasot_dam_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n 7:00 AM - 6:00 PM.</string>
    <string name="kaliyasot_dam_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="kaliyasot_dam_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_kaliyasot_dam">
     Kaliyasot Dam is one the most prominent dams in Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh. The place is about 13.5 kms away from the Bhopal
     Junction railway station.
    \n\nKaliyasot Dam is primarily used for the irrigation of the farmlands in the immediate areas of Bhopal and Raisen,
        especially for growing rabi crops in the months of November to February. The dam also features as an essential part
        of the process of conserving and controlling the flow of rainwater. The dam has 13 gates through which rainwater is directed
        into the flow of the Kaliyasot river, which eventually merges into the Betwa river. The Kaliyasot Dam is a breath of fresh air
        for residents and tourists in the city of Bhopal. The dam has a large lake with pristine water on one side of it, and dense
        greenery on the other. The spot has also gained popularity as a favourite among road trippers for a quick stopover in between
        long drives. Since the area surrounding the dam is made up of a thick cover of trees, the place is also a prime location for
        spotting a wide variety of birds. Tigers have also been sighted in recent years near the dam.
        \n\nKaliyasot Dam offers its visitors the luxury of choosing to indulge in some physical activity or to simply sit
        and take in the silence and the scenery. The best time to visit is during the months of winter for a sunny day on the
        waterside. Visitors can easily spend up to 1 or 2 hours at the place.
        \n\nKaliyasot Dam is not just one of Bhopal\'s major water management projects, but also an enchanting tourist spot.
        The dam and its surrounding area are perfect for an early morning jog or a light stroll later in the evening.
    </string>


    <!-- Kamlanehru udyan -->
    <string name="kamlanehru_udyan">Kamla Nehru Park</string>
    <string name="kamlanehru_udyan_address"> Eastern Rd of BHEL, \nSector A, Berkheda, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462022
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="kamlanehru_udyan_opening_hours">All days of the week except Tuesday
        \n 4:00 AM - 8:00 PM.</string>
    <string name="kamlanehru_udyan_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="kamlanehru_udyan_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_kamlanehru_udyan">
    Kamla Nehru Bal Udhyan is a public park near BHEL township, Sector A in Berkheda, Bhopal. The park is located in the heart of Bhopal.
        Kamla Nehru Bal Udhyan is within city-limits and is easily reachable by road.
        \nKamla Nehru Bal Udhyan is a public and children\'s park in BHEL township located in Bhopal. It is one of the best children
        garden in the city. There is a toy train inside the park which can be enjoyed by the toddlers. Other amenities which the park
        provides are special kids play area, swings, rope bridge and a walking path for morning walk and jogging. The place also doubles
        up as a picnic area where families can enjoy their weekend and the young ones can enjoy with many fun activities the place provides.
        \n\nVisitors should visit the place for the well maintained services which will not only make children happy but will give
        peace to the adults as well. Walking in the garden can boost the vitality of mind and lungs as there is a lot of greenery and
        the garden is full of trees.
    </string>


    <!-- Tribal museum -->
    <string name="tribal_museum">Tribal Museum</string>
    <string name="tribal_museum_address"> Shyamla Hills Rd, Near State Museum, \nShymala Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462002
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="tribal_museum_opening_hours">All days of the week except Tuesday
        \n 12:00 PM - 8:00 PM.</string>
    <string name="tribal_museum_entry_fees">* Indian Visitors: INR 10 per person (10 years &amp; Above).
\n* Foreign Visitors: INR 100 per person (10 years &amp; Above).
\n* Photography: INR 50 (Camera without stand/tripod/flash).
    </string>
    <string name="tribal_museum_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_tribal_museum">
    The Madhya Pradesh Tribal Museum nullifies the gap between the mythical belief of the Tribal population and the evolving
        urbanization. The museum gives you a peak into the psychology of the Tribal people, their practices, games and interpretation
        of life.
        \n\nLearn about the Baiga, Gond, Saharia, Kol, Korko and Bharia tribes of India. Don\’t forget to see the exhibits made from
        terracotta, hollows of dried gourd, hemp and papier-mache. The gallery is quiet a visual treat for art lovers.
    </string>


    <!-- Tribal museum -->
    <string name="madhai">The Madhai Resort</string>
    <string name="madhai_address">Saharanpur Rd, Sohagpur, \nMadhya Pradesh 461771
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="madhai_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \nOpen 24 hours</string>
    <string name="madhai_entry_fees">(**NA**)
    </string>
    <string name="madhai_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_madhai">
    Madhai is located at the entrance of the most exquisite and beautiful forests in India - Satpura.
        Few places in the world can compete with its raw wilderness, absolute tranquillity and the air of mystique.
        It delights you with its rich wildlife, sprawling meadows, unending backwaters and spell-binding views that
        leave you awestruck and get you to be completely in sync with the magic of nature
    </string>


    <!-- Hathaikheda dam -->
    <string name="hathaikheda_dam">hathaikheda Dam</string>
    <string name="hathaikheda_dam_address">Piplani Rd, Piplani, Anandnagar, Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462021
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="hathaikheda_dam_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \nOpen 24 hours</string>
    <string name="hathaikheda_dam_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="hathaikheda_dam_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_hathaikheda_dam">
    Hathaikheda is a dam on the outskirts of City of bhopal and is kind of a local picnic spot.
    </string>


    <!--Katara Hill Botanical Garden -->
    <string name="katara_hill_botanical_garden">Katara Hill Botanical Garden</string>
    <string name="katara_hill_botanical_garden_address">botanical garden near, \nKatara Hills, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="katara_hill_botanical_garden_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n6:00AM to 6:00PM</string>
    <string name="katara_hill_botanical_garden_entry_fees">No Entry Fee
    </string>
    <string name="katara_hill_botanical_garden_visit_duration">1 to 2 Hours</string>
    <string name="about_katara_hill_botanical_garden">
    Katara hill botanical garden is situated in katara hill bhopal. There are many types of plants. Best place
        for nature lover. It opens on all days of the week from 6:00AM to 6:00PM. Best time for visiting this
        place is 2:00PM to 4:PM.
    </string>


    <!--Hotel Rajhansh-->
    <string name="hotel_rajhansh">Rajhans Restaurant</string>
    <string name="hotel_rajhansh_address">Plot No 12 Inter State Bus Terminal \n[ISBT, near Chetak Bridge, behind Nexa Showroom,
        \nCircle, Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462023
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="hotel_rajhansh_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \nMon- 6:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    \nTue-Sun - 10:00 AM - 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="hotel_rajhansh_cuisines">Indian, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_rajhansh_special_diet_meals">* Vegetarian Friendly, \n* Vegan Options, \n* Gluten Free Options\n\nMeals
    \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch
    </string>
    <string name="feature_hotel_rajhansh">
    Takeout, \nReservations, \nSeating, \nTable Service
    </string>

   
    <!--Hong kong Restaurants-->
    <string name="hong_kong">Hong Kong Chinese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="hong_kong_address">No 131/4 Maharana Pratap, Bhopal 462011
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="hong_kong_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n11:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="hong_kong_cuisines">Chinese, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="hong_kong_special_diet_meals">
    Lunch,\nDinner
    </string>
    <string name="feature_hong_kong">
    Seating
    </string>
    
    
    
    <!--Amer bakery Hut-->
    <string name="amer_bakery_hut">Amer Bakery Hut</string>
    <string name="amer_bakery_hut_address"> Branch I:-\nZone-I, 209, Hoshangabad Rd,
        \nDB City Mall, Zone-I,
        \nMaharana Pratap Nagar, Bhopal,
        \nMadhya Pradesh 462023

        \n\nBranch II:-\nPrakash Swimming Pool Campus
        \nLink Main Road No 1, opp.
        \nArera Club, New Market,
        \nSTT Nagar, Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462016

        \n\nBranch III:-\nBittan Market, Sivay Complex,
        \nOpposite Habibganj Police Station,
        \nE-5, Arera Colony, Bhopal,
        \nMadhya Pradesh 462016


 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="amer_bakery_hut_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n9:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="amer_bakery_hut_cuisines">Fast food, \nIndian
    </string>
    <string name="amer_bakery_hut_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options\n\nMeals
        \n* Breakfast, \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner
    </string>
    <string name="feature_amer_bakery_hut">
    Takeout\nSeating
    </string>


    <!-- Shaan E Bhopal Rail Restaurant-->
    <string name="shaan_e_bhopal_rail_restaurant">Shaan E Bhopal Rail Restaurant</string>
    <string name="shaan_e_bhopal_rail_restaurant_address">Hotel Lake View Campus, Shymala Hills, \nBhopal, Madhya Pradesh 462013
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="shaan_e_bhopal_rail_restaurant_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n12:00 PM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="shaan_e_bhopal_rail_restaurant_cuisines">Indian, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="shaan_e_bhopal_rail_restaurant_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options\n\nMeals
        \n* Dinner, \n* Lunch, \n* After-hours
    </string>
    <string name="feature_shaan_e_bhopal_rail_restaurant">
   Reservations, \nSeating, \nParking Available, \nServes Alcohol, \nTable Service, \nValidated Parking, \nLive Music
    </string>


    <!--Sharma and Vishnu Chinese and Fast Food-->
    <string name="sharma_and_vishnu">Sharma and Vishnu Chinese and Fast Food
</string>
    <string name="sharma_and_vishnu_address">Gufa Mandir Road Opposite Domino\'s , \nNear Axis Bank, Bhopal 462032
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="sharma_and_vishnu_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n09:30 AM - 11:30 PM
    </string>
    <string name="sharma_and_vishnu_cuisines">Chinese, \nAsian, \nFast food
    </string>
    <string name="sharma_and_vishnu_special_diet_meals">
    Vegetarian Friendly\n\nMeals
        \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch
    </string>
    <string name="feature_sharma_and_vishnu">
   Seating
    </string>


    <!--Sagar Gaire-->
    <string name="sagar_gaire">Sagar Gaire
</string>
    <string name="sagar_gaire_address">Shop No, BDA Complex, 101, \n7 Number Chouraha, Stop, \nShivaji Nagar, Bhopal, \nMadhya Pradesh 462016
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="sagar_gaire_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n11:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="sagar_gaire_cuisines">Indian, \nFast food, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="sagar_gaire_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options\n\nMeals
    Lunch, \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch
    </string>
    <string name="feature_sagar_gaire">
   Takeout, \nAccepts Credit Cards, \nSeating
    </string>


    <!--Bapu Ki Kutia-->
    <string name="bapu_ki_kutia">Bapu Ki Kutia
</string>
    <string name="bapu_ki_kutia_address">New Market Roshanpura, \nBhopal Madhya Pradesh462003
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bapu_ki_kutia_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n10:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="bapu_ki_kutia_cuisines">Indian, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="bapu_ki_kutia_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options,\n* Gluten Free Options\n\nMeals
    Lunch, \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch\n* After-hours
    </string>
    <string name="feature_bapu_ki_kutia">
   Delivery, \nTakeout, \nReservations, \nSeating, \nParking Available, \nTable Service
    </string>


    <!--Momo Cafe-->
    <string name="momo_cafe">Momo Cafe
</string>
    <string name="momo_cafe_address">DB City - Arera Hills Courtyard by Marriott, \nBhopal, Bhopal 462011
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="momo_cafe_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n06:30 AM - 11:30 PM
    </string>
    <string name="momo_cafe_cuisines">Italian, \nIndian, \nCafe, \nMiddle Eastern, \nInternational, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="momo_cafe_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options,\n* Halal,\n* Gluten Free Options\n\nMeals
    Breakfast,\n* Lunch, \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch\n* After-hours
    </string>
    <string name="feature_momo_cafe">
   Takeout, \nReservations, \nPrivate Dining, \nSeating, \nParking Available, \nValidated Parking,
        \nValet Parking, \nTelevision, \nHighchairs Available, \nWheelchair Accessible, \nServes Alcohol,
        \nFull Bar, \nFree Wifi, \nAccepts Credit Cards, \nTable Service, \nBuffet, \nLive Music
    </string>


    <!--Lazeez Hakim-->
    <string name="lazeez_hakim">Lazeez Hakim
</string>
    <string name="lazeez_hakim_address">187/A, Zone-I,\nMP Nagar Zone-1, Bhopal 462063
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="lazeez_hakim_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n011:00 AM - 11:30 PM
    </string>
    <string name="lazeez_hakim_cuisines">Indian
    </string>
    <string name="lazeez_hakim_special_diet_meals">
    * Halal\n\nMeals
    \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner
    </string>
    <string name="feature_lazeez_hakim">
  Seating, \nReservations, \nTable Service
    </string>


    <!--Indian Coffee House-->
    <string name="indian_coffee_house">Indian Coffee House
</string>
    <string name="indian_coffee_house_address">New Market Road, Bhopal 462022
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="indian_coffee_house_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n011:00 AM - 10:30 PM
    </string>
    <string name="indian_coffee_house_cuisines">Indian, \nSouthwestern, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="indian_coffee_house_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options,\n* Gluten Free Options\n\nMeals
    \n* Breakfast, \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch
    </string>
    <string name="feature_indian_coffee_house">
  Seating, \nReservations, \nTable Service
    </string>

    <!--Manohar Dairy and Restaurant-->
    <string name="manohar_dairy_and_restaurant">Manohar Dairy and Restaurant
</string>
    <string name="manohar_dairy_and_restaurant_address">132, Ground Floor, Zone 1 \nMaharana Pratap Nagar, Bhopal 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="manohar_dairy_and_restaurant_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n08:00 AM - 10:45 PM
    </string>
    <string name="manohar_dairy_and_restaurant_cuisines">Indian, \nFast food, \nStreet Food
    </string>
    <string name="manohar_dairy_and_restaurant_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly,\n* Vegan Options,\n* Gluten Free Options\n\nMeals
    \n* Breakfast, \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner, \n* Brunch
    </string>
    <string name="feature_manohar_dairy_and_restaurant">
  Delivery, \nTakeout, \nSeating, \nStreet \nParking, \nAccepts Mastercard, \nAccepts Visa, \nAccepts Credit Cards, \nTable Service
    </string>


    <!--Bake N Shake-->
    <string name="bake_n_shake">Bake N Shake
</string>
    <string name="bake_n_shake_address">Rangmahal Cineplex Compound , \nNew Market , Bhopal 462002
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="bake_n_shake_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n11:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="bake_n_shake_cuisines">Cafe, \nFast food
    </string>
    <string name="bake_n_shake_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly\n\nMeals
    \n* Breakfast, \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner
    </string>
    <string name="feature_bake_n_shake">
  Takeout, \nSeating
    </string>


    <!--Zam Zam-->
    <string name="zam_zam">Zam Zam
</string>
    <string name="zam_zam_address">Hamidia Road Opposite Corporation Bank, \nBhopal 462001
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="zam_zam_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n11:00 AM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="zam_zam_cuisines">Indian, \nFast food, \nBarbecue, \nAsian
    </string>
    <string name="zam_zam_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly, \n* Halal\n\nMeals
    \n* Dinner
    </string>
    <string name="feature_zam_zam">
  Takeout,
    </string>


    <!--Under The Mango Tree-->
    <string name="under_the_mango_tree">Under The Mango Tree
</string>
    <string name="under_the_mango_tree_address">Jehan Numa Palace 157, \nShamla Hills, Bhopal 462013
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="under_the_mango_tree_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n07:00 PM - 11:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="under_the_mango_tree_cuisines">Indian, \nBarbecue, \nAsian, \nBar, \nPub, \nSoups
    </string>
    <string name="under_the_mango_tree_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly, \n* Vegan Options, \n* Gluten Free Options\n\nMeals
    \n* Dinner, \nAfter-hours
    </string>
    <string name="feature_under_the_mango_tree">
  Takeout, \nReservations, \nOutdoor Seating, \nSeating, \nParking Available, \nValidated Parking, \nValet Parking,
        \nWheelchair Accessible, \nServes Alcohol, \nFull Bar, \nFree Wifi, \nTable Service, \nHighchairs Available
    </string>


    <!--La Kuchina-->
    <string name="la_kuchina">La Kuchina
</string>
    <string name="la_kuchina_address">157, Shamla Hills Jehan Numa Palace Hotel, Bhopal 462013
 \nIndia</string>
    <string name="la_kuchina_opening_hours">All days of the week
        \n12:30 PM - 03:00 PM
    </string>
    <string name="la_kuchina_cuisines">Italian, \nPizza, \nMediterranean
    </string>
    <string name="la_kuchina_special_diet_meals">
    * Vegetarian Friendly, \n* Vegan Options,\n\nMeals
    \n* Lunch, \n* Dinner
    </string>
    <string name="feature_la_kuchina">
    Takeout, \nReservations, \nSeating, \nHighchairs Available, \nServes Alcohol, \nParking Available, \nFull Bar, \nTable Service
    </string>

</resources>
